Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part II WAG.025.002
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Immigration, Resettlement and Refugee Aid
  - Subseries IV:A: General Files
    - 2. Individual Files, arranged alphabetically by name
      - Goldman, Motl, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 180)
      - Goldshmler, Moses, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 181)
      - Goldstein, Baruch, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 182)
      - Goldstein, Bernard, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 183)
      - Goldstein, Sara, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 184)
      - Goldstein, Szmul, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 185)
      - Golom, Mojese, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 186)
      - Gonda, Henryk, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 187)
      - Gordin, Abba Mayer, 1953-1954 (Box 103, Folder 188)
      - Gordon, Jacob, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 189)
      - Gordon, Meilach, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 190)
      - Gothajner, Chaim, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 191)
      - Gotkin, Max, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 192)
      - Gotlib, Chamis, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 193)
      - Gottcheiner, Mortcha and Idesa, 1953 (Box 103, Folder 194)
      - Grebler, Arthur, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 195)
      - Grinbaum, David, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 196)
      - Grinszpan, Israel, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 197)
      - Grinwald, Aba, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 198)
      - Grodzicki, Szlama, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 199)
      - Groschler, Max, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 200)
      - Grosfater, Saul, 1952-1956 (Box 103, Folder 201)
      - Grossman, Menachim, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 202)
      - Grynbaum, Froim, undated (Box 103, Folder 203)
      - Grynberg, Aron, 1949 (Box 103, Folder 204)
      - Gutman, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 205)
      - Haidenblitt, Szyja, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 206)
      - Haut, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 207)
      - Hecht, Leon, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 208)
      - Hecht, Wolek, undated (Box 103, Folder 209)
      - Hendelberg, Isaac, 1950 (Box 103, Folder 210)
      - Henig, Kania, undated (Box 103, Folder 211)
      - Henig, Mendl and Helen, 1954 (Box 103, Folder 212)
      - Herschemfus, Abraham Aaron, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 213)
      - Herszlikowitz, Abram, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 214)
      - Hertz, Rella, 1948 (Box 103, Folder 215)
      - Hildegarde, Walter, 1951 (Box 103, Folder 216)
      - Hilkowitz, Maka, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 217)
      - Hiller, Jakob, 1949-1954 (Box 104, Folder 218)
      - Himelberg, Dora, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 219)
      - Hirsch, Mojszes, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 220)
      - Hoffman, Evzen, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 221)
      - Holcman, Elka, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 222)
      - Horn, Chiel Majer, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 223)
      - Horowicz, Irmgard, undated (Box 104, Folder 224)
      - Horowitz, Elias, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 225)
      - Huberman, Leo, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 226)
      - Imerglueck, Juma, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 227)
      - Infeld, Izak, 1946-1947 (Box 104, Folder 228)
      - Jaffe, Efroim, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 229)
      - Jaffe, Ludwig, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 230)
      - Jagodzinski, Abram, undated (Box 104, Folder 231)
      - Jakubowicz, Jakub, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 232)
      - Jakubowitz, Ancsel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 233)
      - Jalowcer, Chaim, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 234)
      - Jankelewicz, Izrael, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 235)
      - Jasny, Szmul, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 236)
      - Jelen, Ajzyk, 1948-1950 (Box 104, Folder 237)
      - Jerosolimski, David, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 238)
      - Jerozolimski, Szaja, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 239)
      - Jewzerow, Wolf, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 240)
      - Jordon, Paul, 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 241)
      - (Fryderyk Jakub Einaugler), undated (Box 104, Folder 242)
      - Josef, Ethel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 243)
      - Josefsberg, Chana, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 244)
      - Jura, Adela, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 245)
      - Jura, Jerzy, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 246)
      - Jura, Zofja, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 247)
      - Kagan, Mendel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 248)
      - Kahan, Arkadiusz, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 249)
      - Kalfus, Chaim, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 250)
      - Kalinski, Abram, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 251)
      - Kalinski, Hersch, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 252)
      - Kalman, Chait, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 253)
      - Kamermacher, J. W., 1947-1949 (Box 104, Folder 254)
      - Kaner, Abraham, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 255)
      - Kaner, Simon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 256)
      - Kanter, Isaac Dr., 1951 (Box 104, Folder 257)
      - Kanter, Reisl (Zychlinska), 1954 (Box 104, Folder 258)
      - Karten, David, undated (Box 104, Folder 259)
      - Kartsch, Beniek and Chawa, undated (Box 104, Folder 260)
      - Katschanowska, Nechama, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 261)
      - Katz, Jakob, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 262)
      - Katz, Josef, undated (Box 104, Folder 263)
      - Katz, Masza, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 264)
      - Kaufman, Jehuda, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 265)
      - Kazmierski, Solomon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 266)
      - Kelman, Burach, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 267)
      - Kerschenblat, Moishe, undated (Box 104, Folder 268)
      - Kestenberg, Max, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 269)
      - Kleidermacher, Sarah, 1951-1955 (Box 104, Folder 270)
      - Klinger, Bertha, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 271)
      - Klok, Sima, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 272)
      - Knecht, Iser-Leizor, undated (Box 104, Folder 273)
      - Knecht, Sije-Mordka, undated (Box 104, Folder 274)
      - Kohn, Adolf, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 275)
      - Kohn, Mojsze, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 276)
      - Kolman, Tscheslawa, 1949-1950 (Box 104, Folder 277)
      - Koplowicz, Dawid, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 278)
      - Koplowicz, Kopel, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 279)
      - Koral, Rubin, 1954-1956 (Box 104, Folder 280)
      - Korn, Markus, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 281)
      - Korn, Rochel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 282)
      - Kornhauser, Jakob, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 283)
      - Kosover, Sophie, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 284)
      - Koszer, Natan, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 285)
      - Kozak, Moses, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 286)
      - Kra, Jankel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 287)
      - Kramer, Jehuda, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 288)
      - Kramer, Zelda, undated (Box 104, Folder 289)
      - Krasner, Towia, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 290)
      - Krausman, Samuel Pinkus, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 291)
      - Krel, Abram, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 292)
      - Krel, Peritz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 293)
      - Krischer, Benno, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 294)
      - Krol, Regina (Riwka Eidl), 1951 (Box 104, Folder 295)
      - Krotowski, Benek, undated (Box 104, Folder 296)
      - Kruk, Alta, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 297)
      - Kryger, Wolf, undated (Box 104, Folder 298)
      - Krzepicki, Majer, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 299)
      - Kulike, Willy, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 300)
      - Kunda, Faiga, 1952-1956 (Box 104, Folder 301)
      - Kuperwaser, Hersz, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 302)
      - Kurenitz, Rywa (Rebecca), 1948 (Box 104, Folder 303)
      - Kurland, Abraham, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 304)
      - Kurz, Jacob, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 305)
      - Kwiat, David, 1948, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 306)
      - Lande, Leo, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 307)
        Microfilm reel#: 303
      - Landsman, Lazar, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 308)
      - Lang, Joseph, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 309)
      - Lap, Moses, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 310)
      - Latrowski, Bluma, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 311)
      - Lebovitz, Dave, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 312)
      - Lebovitz, Jan, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 313)
      - Lebovitz, Moses, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 314)
      - Lederman, Abraham, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 315)
      - Lederman, Binem, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 316)
      - Lefkowitz, Icek, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 317)
      - Lefkowitz, Samuel and Klara, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 318)
      - Leibinger, Avrum, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 319)
      - Leiser, Friedrich, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 320)
      - Lenkinski, Lajzer, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 321)
      - Lerner, Saul, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 322)
      - Leslie, Margueretta Olga, 1956 (Box 104, Folder 323)
      - Levitan, Atler, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 324)
      - Lew, Lejzer, undated (Box 104, Folder 325)
      - Lewin, Izak, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 326)
      - Lewkowicz, Fela, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 327)
      - Lewkowicz, Ignac, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 328)
      - Lewkowitz, Srulek, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 329)
      - Liebeskind, Chaim, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 330)
      - Liebeskind, Izrael-Wolf, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 331)
      - Lifszyc, Feiwel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 332)
      - Ligorski, Elias, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 333)
      - Linenberg, Faiwel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 334)
      - Linkomir, Abraham, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 335)
      - Lipkowicz, Moniek, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 336)
      - Lipshitz, Sander, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 337)
      - Lipski, Felix, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 338)
      - Loew, Matilda, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 339)
      - Loike, Chaim, 1954-1955 (Box 104, Folder 340)
      - Lotrowski, Menasze, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 341)
      - Lubinski, Szlama, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 342)
      - Lugorski, David, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 343)
      - Mailman, Sam, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 344)
      - Maisel, Meier, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 345)
      - Maitlis, Jacob, 1948-1953 (Box 104, Folder 346)
      - Majzler, Jacob, undated (Box 104, Folder 347)
      - Malinowski, Jonasz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 348)
      - Mangel, Dora, 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 349)
      - Marczak, Zygmunt, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 350)
      - Margulies, Herman, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 351)
      - Mariampolski, Abram, undated (Box 104, Folder 352)
      - Markowicz, Jones, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 353)
      - Markowitz, Fajwel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 354)
      - Markus, Leizer, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 355)
      - Maurer, Salomon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 356)
      - Maxamine, Leopold, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 357)
      - Meisels, Rabbi Samu, 1950-1951 (Box 104, Folder 358)
      - Meisler, Regina, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 359)
      - Mejer, Melech-Chaim, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 360)
      - Mentlik, Berke, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 361)
      - Merkado, Ottilija, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 362)
      - Meyer, Frieda, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 363)
      - Micenmacher, Rosa, undated (Box 104, Folder 364)
      - Miller, Jacob, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 365)
      - Minc, Isak, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 366)
      - Minikes, Mayer, 1949-1950 (Box 104, Folder 367)
      - Minster, David, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 368)
      - Mlotek, Abraham, 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 369)
      - Moncznik, Abraham, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 370)
      - Moncznik, Hersz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 371)
      - Moncznik, Mozes, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 372)
      - Monowicz, Israel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 373)
      - Mordkowicz, Chackel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 374)
      - Morgenstern, Icchok, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 375)
      - Mosak, Benjamin, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 376)
      - Moschkowitz, Chaim, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 377)
      - Mydlarz, Jakob, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 378)
      - Mysch, Mordka, undated (Box 104, Folder 379)
      - Nachman, Judah, 1955 (Box 104, Folder 380)
      - Nachmanowicz, Pinkus, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 381)
      - Nadler, Sadie, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 382)
      - Najda, Jean, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 383)
      - Natanblit, Anna, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 384)
      - Natowitz, Leonhard, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 385)
      - Nesig, Jacob, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 386)
      - Neuman, Fiszel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 387)
      - Nicinski, Josef, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 388)
      - Nicinski, Samuel, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 389)
      - Noremberski, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 390)
      - Norman, Boris, undated (Box 104, Folder 391)
      - Nowak, Moritz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 392)
      - Nowodgrodzki, Emanuel, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 393)
      - Novak, Shale, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 394)
      - Nudelman, Israel, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 395)
      - Ofman, Ezro, undated (Box 104, Folder 396)
      - Oksman, Abram, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 397)
      - Olberg, Izak, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 398)
      - Oldziejewski, Stanislaw, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 399)
      - Oler, Riva, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 400)
      - Olicki, Mates, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 401)
      - Opoczynski, Arja, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 402)
      - Opoczynski, Leib-Ber, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 403)
      - Ordynans, Hersz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 404)
      - Pankowsky, Hanna, 1952 (Box 104, Folder 405)
      - Papier, Majer, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 406)
      - Papierbuch, Jakub, undated (Box 104, Folder 407)
      - Pasternak, Herman, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 408)
      - Pausch, Anna, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 409)
      - Pelta, Chaim, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 410)
      - Peres, Laja, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 411)
      - Petkov, George, 1953 (Box 104, Folder 412)
      - Piekarz, Lejba, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 413)
      - Pinkusewicz, Wolf, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 414)
      - Piwko, Alter, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 415)
      - Pollak, Kalman, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 416)
      - Portnoj, Hersz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 417)
      - Poziomke, Hersh and Gerszon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 418)
      - Propinator, Icek, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 419)
      - Pulwermacher, Abram, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 420)
      - Putermilch, Hersz, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 421)
      - Rabinowitz, Letzer, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 422)
      - Rafalowicz, Halina, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 423)
      - Rajan, Abraham, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 424)
      - Rac, Abe, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 425)
      - Rakocznski, Mozes, 1945, 1951-1952 (Box 104, Folder 426)
      - Rapaport, Moses, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 427)
      - Rapoport, Lajos, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 428)
      - Ratkovich, Alexander, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 429)
      - Rauch, Leisor, 1951-1954 (Box 104, Folder 430)
      - Reinbach, Max, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 431)
      - Reinhartz,Iser, 1954 (Box 104, Folder 432)
      - Reischer, Dawid, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 433)
      - Reznick, Wolf, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 434)
      - Richter, George, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 435)
      - Ritter, Marcus, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 436)
      - Rohloff, Dagmar, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 437)
      - Rohloff, Nathan, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 438)
      - Rohloff, Thea, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 439)
      - Ramonowicz, Abram, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 440)
      - Rosen, Herman, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 441)
      - Rosenbaum, Margareta, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 442)
      - Rosenberg, Leon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 443)
      - Rosenberg, Mordka, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 444)
      - Rosenberg, Moses-Mietek, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 445)
      - Rosenblat, Motek, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 446)
      - Rosenblum, Boris, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 447)
      - Rosenblum, Leib, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 448)
      - Rosenblum, Lejzor, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 449)
      - Rosenstein, David, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 450)
      - Rosenzweig, Salomon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 451)
      - Rosner, Janina, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 452)
      - Rosner, Marta, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 453)
      - Rotblit, Israel, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 454)
      - Rotenbach, Cecilia, 1954-1956 (Box 104, Folder 455)
      - Rotenberg, Dawid, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 456)
      - Rotenberg, Natan, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 457)
      - Rotenberg, Sala, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 458)
      - Rotenberg-Finkelstein, Joseph, 1951 (Box 104, Folder 459)
      - Rothkopf, Szaja, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 460)
      - Rothstein, Rebecca, 1951-1954 (Box 104, Folder 461)
      - Rotstein, Jakob, 1948-1948 (Box 104, Folder 462)
      - Rotstein, Maria, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 463)
      - Rottenberg, Abraham, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 464)
      - Rottenberg, Rachelle, 1952-1953 (Box 104, Folder 465)
      - Rozenbaum, Szymon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 466)
      - Rozencwajg, Benjamin, undated (Box 104, Folder 467)
      - Rubinstein, Israel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 468)
      - Rubinstein, Szloma, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 469)
      - Rudzki, Hersz, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 470)
      - Rybak, Izak, 1949, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 471)
      - Safier, Isser, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 472)
      - Safier, Rubin, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 473)
      - Sandler, Moyze, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 474)
      - Sapersztein, Simon, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 475)
      - Sapoznik, Zindel, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 476)
      - Savicki, Jakob, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 477)
      - Schacter, Israel, 1948-1949 (Box 104, Folder 478)
      - Schaibe, Moshe, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 479)
      - Schapit, Michael, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 480)
      - Scheinbach, Herman, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 481)
      - Schibuk, Paula H. M., 1953-1954 (Box 104, Folder 482)
      - Schichter, Natan, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 483)
      - Schidlowski, Izaak, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 484)
      - Schiff, Ladislaw, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 485)
      - Schlachtman, David, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 486)
      - Schneider, Emil, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 487)
      - Schoss, Josef, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 488)
      - Schpiro, Natan, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 489)
      - Schredni, Jankel, 1950 (Box 104, Folder 490)
      - Schwartz, Mendel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 491)
      - Schwartz, Szyja, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 492)
      - Schwartz-Peltyn, Salomea (Mrs.), 1948 (Box 104, Folder 493)
      - Schwarz, Chaim, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 494)
      - Schwarz, Solomon M., undated (Box 104, Folder 495)
      - Schwarzenberg, Chil, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 496)
      - Segal, Moses, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 497)
      - Segal, Pinchos, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 498)
      - Seidman, David (Mrs.), 1948 (Box 104, Folder 499)
      - Seinityki, Rachmiel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 500)
      - Selske, Fischel, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 501)
      - Selske, Laia, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 502)
      - Sendowska, Laja, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 503)
      - Shatzkin, J., 1948 (Box 104, Folder 504)
      - Shea, Albert, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 505)
      - Shimaite, Anna, 1951-1952 (Box 104, Folder 506)
      - Sibirsky, Itzik, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 507)
      - Siegfried, Isakus, 1947-1948 (Box 104, Folder 508)
      - Sienitzki, Rachmiel M., 1948 (Box 104, Folder 509)
      - Siew, Boruch, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 510)
      - Silbiger, Emil, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 511)
      - Silman, Meyer and Ides, 1949 (Box 104, Folder 512)
      - Singer, Emil, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 513)
      - Singer, Hena, 1948 (Box 104, Folder 514)
      - Sipeki, Rosalia, 1955-1956 (Box 104, Folder 515)
      - Sirotko, Kopel-Mozes, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 516)
        Microfilm reel#: 304
      - Skiba, Edward, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 517)
      - Sklarz, Mordka, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 518)
      - Skuvecki, Joel, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 519)
      - Sokolow, Heniek, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 520)
      - Solski, Joel, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 521)
      - Sonabend, Herman, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 522)
      - Sonnenschein, Benjamin, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 523)
      - Sonnenschein, Irene, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 524)
      - Sorger, Samuel, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 525)
      - Spewinski, Hersz (Henryk), 1948 (Box 105, Folder 526)
      - Spiewak, Josef, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 527)
      - Spitz, Alfred, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 528)
      - Sredni, Josef, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 529)
      - Sroka, Beno, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 530)
      - Sroka, Nellie Stern, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 531)
      - Stal, Lew, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 532)
      - Stauber, Martin, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 533)
      - Steinhorn, Herman, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 534)
      - Stelnick, Josef, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 535)
      - Stok, Brania, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 536)
      - Stosser, David, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 537)
      - Stosser, Sara, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 538)
      - Swenzenowicz, Moisze, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 539)
      - Swiel, Jacob, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 540)
      - Sylvia, James, 1949-1950 (Box 105, Folder 541)
      - Szajbowicz, Gabriel, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 542)
      - Szajko, Josef, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 543)
      - Szajner, Isak, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 544)
      - Szapsik (Silberasjain), Isak, 1952-1955 (Box 105, Folder 545)
      - Szeinman, Mordke, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 546)
      - Szek, Hersz, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 547)
      - Szlamowicz, Zalmem, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 548)
      - Szrajeman, Derek, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 549)
      - Szteinberg, Szlama, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 550)
      - Szulman, Abram, 1960 (Box 105, Folder 551)
      - Szwaiko, Aram, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 552)
      - Szwarcberg, Gerszon, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 553)
      - Szwarckopf, Uszer, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 554)
      - Szwimer, Mordko, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 555)
      - Szylis, Hirsch, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 556)
      - Tager, Isaak (aka Martin Gerson), 1955 (Box 105, Folder 557)
      - Tarasiejski, Benjamin-Benedykt, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 558)
      - Tarcownik, Karol, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 559)
      - Tellerman, Jakob, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 560)
      - Tepper, Aron, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 561)
      - Tikulski, Jakob, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 562)
      - Topel, Rosalie (Chanachowicz), 1955 (Box 105, Folder 563)
      - Treu, Fritz, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 564)
      - Uriewicz, Zalmen, 1956 (Box 105, Folder 565)
      - Vanovsky, Alexander, 1947-1948 (Box 105, Folder 566)
      - Vidushinski, Benjamin, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 567)
      - Wachtel, Harry and Erna, 1954-1955 (Box 105, Folder 568)
      - Wajcman, Leiser, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 569)
      - Waksmann, Szulem, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 570)
      - Walkarz, Leizer, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 571)
      - Wapner, Paja, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 572)
      - Warszawska, Stefania, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 573)
      - Warzecha, David, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 574)
      - Wasserman, Fajwel, undated (Box 105, Folder 575)
      - Weingarten, Feiga, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 576)
      - Weinglein, Elli, undated (Box 105, Folder 577)
      - Weinreb, Meier, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 578)
      - Weinreb, Stefania, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 579)
      - Weinstock, Aron, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 580)
      - Weisman, Dawid, 1948-1949 (Box 105, Folder 581)
      - Weisner, Henrietta, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 582)
      - Weiss, Andor, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 583)
      - Weiss, Jeno, 1948-1949 (Box 105, Folder 584)
      - Weliczker, Leon, 1949-1950 (Box 105, Folder 585)
      - Wichter, Josef, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 586)
      - Wiener, Frieda, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 587)
      - Wilenski, M., 1950 (Box 105, Folder 588)
      - Wilk, Jacob, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 589)
      - Wisel, Leon, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 590)
      - Wolfowicz, Maks, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 591)
      - Wolman, Izak and Family, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 592)
      - Wurm, Mania, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 593)
      - Yoskonitz, Szymon, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 594)
      - Zabielski, Gerson, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 595)
      - Zalcberg, Lajb, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 596)
      - Zalcman, Gerszon, 1947-1948 (Box 105, Folder 597)
      - Zalewitz, Ben Zion, 1952 (Box 105, Folder 598)
      - Zarembok, Abram, 1948-1949 (Box 105, Folder 599)
      - Zarenbok, Mendel, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 600)
      - Zegrze, Herman, 1939-1946 (Box 105, Folder 601)
      - Zeidenwurm, Chaim, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 602)
      - Zeleznik, David, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 603)
      - Zeltner, Schepsel, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 604)
      - Zenderland, Hemia, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 605)
      - Zimelman, Szmul, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 606)
      - Zlotnik, Kielman, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 607)
      - Zoladz, Szaja, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 608)
      - Zolna, Israel, 1949-1950 (Box 105, Folder 609)
      - Zolna, Josef, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 610)
      - Zycherman, Majer, undated (Box 105, Folder 611)
      - Zygiel, Chaim David, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 612)
      - Zylberberg, Berek, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 613)
      - Zylberberg, Leizer, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 614)
      - Zylberberg, Wolf, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 615)
      - Zylberszac, Tauba, 1948 (Box 105, Folder 616)
    - 3. General Correspondence (filed by letter of the alphabet, and then chronologically)
      (These files follow the unnumbered individual files, in the same box.)
      - A, [1947], 1948 (Box 105, Folder 1)
      - A, 1949 (Box 105, Folder 2)
      - A, 1950 (Box 105, Folder 3)
      - A, 1951 (Box 105, Folder 4)